<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Income Boss]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Income Boss]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:40:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Did the Switch to WPEngine Boost My SEO Performance? [CASE STUDY] ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Did the Switch to WPEngine Boost My SEO Performance? [CASE STUDY] </h1><p>Get the number 1 recommended website hosting and builder on the planet. Period!</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a4708236ee19c89ec369eff7b43da70351dd05c3.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/did-the-switch-to-wpengine-boost-my-seo-performance-case-s/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a3613e05-a2f8-4e57-8684-58a003ae1dac</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 02:56:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HOW I WENT FROM 0 TO 25K/MO WITH THE HELP OF THIS STRATEGY]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>HOW I WENT FROM 0 TO 25K/MO WITH THE HELP OF THIS STRATEGY</h1><p>Throughout my time of running an agency, I’ve tried just about every prospecting method you can imagine. From networking to content marketing and even paying people to hand out flyers – it all seemed to be just mediocre.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/how-i-went-from-0-to-25kmo-with-the-help-of-this-strategy/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9323b7b0-ba27-425e-986f-e15d1cf82315</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:39:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3 Pack Local Stack…What YOU Need To Know To Profit!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>3 Pack Local Stack…What YOU Need To Know To Profit!</h1><p>For consultants, freelancers and business owners, if you use Google as a way to bring in leads for your business in the form of SEO you already know that the landscape changes and will continue to change. You deal with major algorithm changes, shifts in local user experience, even the changing of names i.e. Google Places, Google+ Local and now Google My Business.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/3-pack-local-stackwhat-you-need-to-know-to-profit/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">905103a1-0bf1-4afc-9b8f-198f2d4c15ab</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:28:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[REVIEWS: THE UNDERSTATED VARIABLE IN LOCAL SEO]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>REVIEWS: THE UNDERSTATED VARIABLE IN LOCAL SEO</h1><p>For some reason reviews don’t get a lot of credit when it comes to local SEO. People talk about backlinking, citation building, on page optimization, map embeds, youtube videos but one of the highest impact things that can be done is harvesting reviews for a business.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/reviews-the-understated-variable-in-local-seo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3d9bdfb1-a896-4017-b469-5c5b86944b8b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cold calling and telemarketing are topics that seem to be an evergreen issue among marketers and many business owners. There’s never any closure on this issue for many though and hopefully this blog post settles some of the issues!So you forum addicts, next time this issue comes up and you’re debating whether it’s effective or not all you have to do is share this post and you instantly win the argument. That’s a fact :)IS COLD CALLING THE ULTIMATE MARKETING STRATEGY?I’m really not against cold calling or telemarketing, I’m also not exactly for it either. The reason I’m not choosing a side is because whether it is right for you or not depends on a multitude of things.Obviously it’s not something every business would use. Can you imagine a locksmith cold calling people or a dental practice making cold calls to sell ClearChoice? Maybe it would work to a certain extent but it isn’t really ideal for everyone is it?I do recommend it as part of my quadruple threat marketing strategy… but is it right for you?WHEN IS COLD CALLING A GOOD IDEA?For some, the answer will be never. I can only comment from the perspective of a web design or marketing company though I’m sure other industries will be different.Cold calling is ideal for people that are:Just starting out and in need of clientsFor those that don’t have money for other advertising methodsFor those in need of a sale, FASTFor those that can afford a scaled telemarketing operationMaking those 4 points or descriptions of ideal candidates for cold calling, I realize it covers a wide spectrum. Let dig into that deeper.WHY IT’S GOOD FOR THOSE STARTING OUT AND IN NEED OF CLIENTS?The first point made was that it’s good for beginners. This is something a lot of people will disagree with because cold calling really isn’t a “beginner strategy”.It’s definitely not easy, but it’s not something you need a lot of knowledge about in order to be successful. In fact, any dummy can do it, I’ve had some very stupid sales people that did very well.The reason it’s good for those starting out, is because it forces you to talk to people about what you’re offering. I don’t care how poorly you perform on the phone, or what ailments you have like a stuttering problem, awkward voice, shyness, as long as you make enough phone calls you will generate leads and when you generate leads you generate sales.WHY IT’S GOOD FOR THOSE THAT DON’T HAVE MONEY FOR OTHER METHODSLook…Nobody wants to cold call. The reason people do it when they start out is usually because they’re broke. That was my case at least and I’ve seen it repeated by countless others out there.All you need is a phone, software to scrape leads or manually find leads to call, and the willingness to dial the numbers.Nothing really complicated.In the USA you don’t need to worry about a do not call list because businesses can not be on a do not call list.It’s simple.Obviously if you have money though you would probably be investing in other methods that bring you inbound calls though, wouldn’t you?It’s cheap… time consuming and something that doesn’t allow you to really multi-task if it’s your only prospecting method but it is certainly cheap!COLD CALLING IS GOOD FOR CLOSING CLIENTS FAST!I know “fast” is relative. Fast for me may be slow for you or fast to you may be slow to me. However, a beginner strategy when cold calling is to separate the duds from the ones that express interest.There’s been many times where clients I’ve cold called were closed within a week of first contact.It’s simply a matter of turning a list of numbers into actual leads that are interested in what you have to offer.Every other form of marketing you’re going to do once you grow, whether it is direct mailing, Craigslist ads, email marketing, pay per click, social media, LinkedIn or whatever other method you want to implement is likely going to take time to generate leads. This is especially true when it comes to inbound marketing.With cold calling, you are taking a proactive approach instead of a passive approach.If you need money to pay the bills, doesn’t it make sense to put yourself out there and try to make something happen instead of waiting around for someone to call you?By no means do I suggest cold calling to be the only legitimate solution when it comes to lead generation but when you’re starting out, it makes sense to actively fill your time with direct tactics.FOR A SCALED OPERATION COLD CALLING WORKS WELLFor larger companies, many of them have a dedicated marketing and advertising budget. What is interesting is that many large corporations still have a telemarketing department. Why? Because it works.These people typically are not paid a high wage, they just make calls and try to meet their quota.Even low skilled employees can bring a positive ROI when it comes to telemarketing.Most telemarketers struggle to make $30,000/year with a company, because it is usually a low wage job and commissions aren’t structured in a way that creates opportunity, but you can bet that the company is getting at least a 200% ROI.It makes sense of them… which makes the concept of cold calling and telemarketing very interesting because there are many other areas where it DOES NOT make any sense to cold call.WHY COLD CALLING ISN’T RIGHT FOR MOST OTHER BUSINESSESI outlined the benefits, who it works for and why.Now it’s time for me to break down exactly why cold calling ISN’T right for most businesses.Want more awesome content to help you grow your business? Email: SubmitIF YOU’RE BEYOND START-UP PHASE, YOU’RE WASTING TIME AND RESOURCES!If you’re a new company low on money of course, cold calling makes sense. However, if you already have a stream of income and you’re growing then it makes sense to put your time and effort into other areas because now your time is more valuable.It’s time for you to make your money work for you.A guy in the Income Bully Skype Group, which is a mastermind group for anyone that buys one of my products like the Ice Cold Email Gold guide for cold email marketing or my Ultimate Blueprint to Start a Web Agency. He’s been doing pretty well with his business, he’s regularly making sales and he’s growing his company.The problem… he’s not going to grow his business by cold calling. Maybe he hasn’t hit the plateau yet but he’s probably very close.As a one man or one woman operation, your time, and resources are going to be stretched. Money continues coming in and your time becomes worth more than a certain amount of money.THAT is when it’s time to start using other methods. After a little bit of talking and explaining, he’s now working on a direct mail campaign that should generate a lot of leads and sales.It costs money… but the money he spends, he will make back from that investment. Time spent cold calling will never come back to him.WHEN YOU STOP COLD CALLING YOU STOP MAKING MONEYWhen you’re making sales, and you’re pulling in some sort of volume besides a random sale here and there you already know it’s time to diversify your marketing efforts.The problem with those that don’t diversify or continue down the solo path of cold calling is that they aren’t really building a business, they simply created a very tedious job.Cold calling has no cumulative effect. There’s no compounding interest that your marketing provides.The second you stop cold calling is the second you stop generating leads and when you’re not generating leads you’re not making money!Get it?It is 100% dependent on you performing that tedious task for the rest of your life.It ISN’T A BUSINESS if it depends on you cold calling every single day in order to survive. It’s just a job.A business is bigger than that, a business is something built to last and something that can operate without you. It has automation involved, processes and systems to make things easier for you, employees, and management.If more than half your income comes from sales generated from cold calling at this stage in the game you’re in trouble!Start looking for marketing strategies that can run without your active participation.COLD CALLING CAN’T BE AUTOMATEDLike I said in the beginning section, there are businesses that can benefit from cold calling, especially very early stages of building a business.There are also very large companies that can benefit from it.However, until you can employ a team of 2-3 people constantly making cold calls on behalf of your company it is no longer a strategy you should be using unless you really have nothing better to do with your time.Sure, some will talk about outsourcing it but no one has success outsourcing their telemarketing. Telemarketers need supervision and you have to be on them to make their calls or else it doesn’t get done properly.At this point though, you should be implementing marketing tactics that you can automate.Think about it… you already deal with project management, completing the work you have, maybe bookkeeping, accounting, and client interaction, support, etc. It’s hard to block off an entire day for cold calling and when you’re cold calling it’s important to “get into a groove” instead of making 1 or 2 calls here and there.Can you justify 8 hours of your day to call 200 people or would you rather spend a few hundred bucks on direct mail and only take up maybe 1 hour of your time? Would you rather block off a week for calling or implement a cold email marketing campaign, direct mail, pay per click with Google and Facebook, retargeting, and attend networking events while maintaining your business and client relationships and every day operations?The answer seems pretty simple to me. There comes a point when cold calling just isn’t an efficient use of your time anymore.BOTTOM LINECold calling can be effective. Nobody can truly deny that but there are different phases and stages of business. Not every process, system or marketing technique is going to be the ideal choice for every stage you enter.There are many situations where cold calling is an ideal choice to grow something from nothing but if you continue only using that stream of lead generation all by yourself you’re bound to be stuck on a plateau and you’re also exposing yourself to a lot of unneeded risk.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Cold calling and telemarketing are topics that seem to be an evergreen issue among marketers and many business owners. There’s never any closure on this issue for many though and hopefully this blog post settles some of the issues!So you forum addicts, next time this issue comes up and you’re debating whether it’s effective or not all you have to do is share this post and you instantly win the argument. That’s a fact :)IS COLD CALLING THE ULTIMATE MARKETING STRATEGY?I’m really not against cold calling or telemarketing, I’m also not exactly for it either. The reason I’m not choosing a side is because whether it is right for you or not depends on a multitude of things.Obviously it’s not something every business would use. Can you imagine a locksmith cold calling people or a dental practice making cold calls to sell ClearChoice? Maybe it would work to a certain extent but it isn’t really ideal for everyone is it?I do recommend it as part of my quadruple threat marketing strategy… but is it right for you?WHEN IS COLD CALLING A GOOD IDEA?For some, the answer will be never. I can only comment from the perspective of a web design or marketing company though I’m sure other industries will be different.Cold calling is ideal for people that are:Just starting out and in need of clientsFor those that don’t have money for other advertising methodsFor those in need of a sale, FASTFor those that can afford a scaled telemarketing operationMaking those 4 points or descriptions of ideal candidates for cold calling, I realize it covers a wide spectrum. Let dig into that deeper.WHY IT’S GOOD FOR THOSE STARTING OUT AND IN NEED OF CLIENTS?The first point made was that it’s good for beginners. This is something a lot of people will disagree with because cold calling really isn’t a “beginner strategy”.It’s definitely not easy, but it’s not something you need a lot of knowledge about in order to be successful. In fact, any dummy can do it, I’ve had some very stupid sales people that did very well.The reason it’s good for those starting out, is because it forces you to talk to people about what you’re offering. I don’t care how poorly you perform on the phone, or what ailments you have like a stuttering problem, awkward voice, shyness, as long as you make enough phone calls you will generate leads and when you generate leads you generate sales.WHY IT’S GOOD FOR THOSE THAT DON’T HAVE MONEY FOR OTHER METHODSLook…Nobody wants to cold call. The reason people do it when they start out is usually because they’re broke. That was my case at least and I’ve seen it repeated by countless others out there.All you need is a phone, software to scrape leads or manually find leads to call, and the willingness to dial the numbers.Nothing really complicated.In the USA you don’t need to worry about a do not call list because businesses can not be on a do not call list.It’s simple.Obviously if you have money though you would probably be investing in other methods that bring you inbound calls though, wouldn’t you?It’s cheap… time consuming and something that doesn’t allow you to really multi-task if it’s your only prospecting method but it is certainly cheap!COLD CALLING IS GOOD FOR CLOSING CLIENTS FAST!I know “fast” is relative. Fast for me may be slow for you or fast to you may be slow to me. However, a beginner strategy when cold calling is to separate the duds from the ones that express interest.There’s been many times where clients I’ve cold called were closed within a week of first contact.It’s simply a matter of turning a list of numbers into actual leads that are interested in what you have to offer.Every other form of marketing you’re going to do once you grow, whether it is direct mailing, Craigslist ads, email marketing, pay per click, social media, LinkedIn or whatever other method you want to implement is likely going to take time to generate leads. This is especially true when it comes to inbound marketing.With cold calling, you are taking a proactive approach instead of a passive approach.If you need money to pay the bills, doesn’t it make sense to put yourself out there and try to make something happen instead of waiting around for someone to call you?By no means do I suggest cold calling to be the only legitimate solution when it comes to lead generation but when you’re starting out, it makes sense to actively fill your time with direct tactics.FOR A SCALED OPERATION COLD CALLING WORKS WELLFor larger companies, many of them have a dedicated marketing and advertising budget. What is interesting is that many large corporations still have a telemarketing department. Why? Because it works.These people typically are not paid a high wage, they just make calls and try to meet their quota.Even low skilled employees can bring a positive ROI when it comes to telemarketing.Most telemarketers struggle to make $30,000/year with a company, because it is usually a low wage job and commissions aren’t structured in a way that creates opportunity, but you can bet that the company is getting at least a 200% ROI.It makes sense of them… which makes the concept of cold calling and telemarketing very interesting because there are many other areas where it DOES NOT make any sense to cold call.WHY COLD CALLING ISN’T RIGHT FOR MOST OTHER BUSINESSESI outlined the benefits, who it works for and why.Now it’s time for me to break down exactly why cold calling ISN’T right for most businesses.Want more awesome content to help you grow your business? Email: SubmitIF YOU’RE BEYOND START-UP PHASE, YOU’RE WASTING TIME AND RESOURCES!If you’re a new company low on money of course, cold calling makes sense. However, if you already have a stream of income and you’re growing then it makes sense to put your time and effort into other areas because now your time is more valuable.It’s time for you to make your money work for you.A guy in the Income Bully Skype Group, which is a mastermind group for anyone that buys one of my products like the Ice Cold Email Gold guide for cold email marketing or my Ultimate Blueprint to Start a Web Agency. He’s been doing pretty well with his business, he’s regularly making sales and he’s growing his company.The problem… he’s not going to grow his business by cold calling. Maybe he hasn’t hit the plateau yet but he’s probably very close.As a one man or one woman operation, your time, and resources are going to be stretched. Money continues coming in and your time becomes worth more than a certain amount of money.THAT is when it’s time to start using other methods. After a little bit of talking and explaining, he’s now working on a direct mail campaign that should generate a lot of leads and sales.It costs money… but the money he spends, he will make back from that investment. Time spent cold calling will never come back to him.WHEN YOU STOP COLD CALLING YOU STOP MAKING MONEYWhen you’re making sales, and you’re pulling in some sort of volume besides a random sale here and there you already know it’s time to diversify your marketing efforts.The problem with those that don’t diversify or continue down the solo path of cold calling is that they aren’t really building a business, they simply created a very tedious job.Cold calling has no cumulative effect. There’s no compounding interest that your marketing provides.The second you stop cold calling is the second you stop generating leads and when you’re not generating leads you’re not making money!Get it?It is 100% dependent on you performing that tedious task for the rest of your life.It ISN’T A BUSINESS if it depends on you cold calling every single day in order to survive. It’s just a job.A business is bigger than that, a business is something built to last and something that can operate without you. It has automation involved, processes and systems to make things easier for you, employees, and management.If more than half your income comes from sales generated from cold calling at this stage in the game you’re in trouble!Start looking for marketing strategies that can run without your active participation.COLD CALLING CAN’T BE AUTOMATEDLike I said in the beginning section, there are businesses that can benefit from cold calling, especially very early stages of building a business.There are also very large companies that can benefit from it.However, until you can employ a team of 2-3 people constantly making cold calls on behalf of your company it is no longer a strategy you should be using unless you really have nothing better to do with your time.Sure, some will talk about outsourcing it but no one has success outsourcing their telemarketing. Telemarketers need supervision and you have to be on them to make their calls or else it doesn’t get done properly.At this point though, you should be implementing marketing tactics that you can automate.Think about it… you already deal with project management, completing the work you have, maybe bookkeeping, accounting, and client interaction, support, etc. It’s hard to block off an entire day for cold calling and when you’re cold calling it’s important to “get into a groove” instead of making 1 or 2 calls here and there.Can you justify 8 hours of your day to call 200 people or would you rather spend a few hundred bucks on direct mail and only take up maybe 1 hour of your time? Would you rather block off a week for calling or implement a cold email marketing campaign, direct mail, pay per click with Google and Facebook, retargeting, and attend networking events while maintaining your business and client relationships and every day operations?The answer seems pretty simple to me. There comes a point when cold calling just isn’t an efficient use of your time anymore.BOTTOM LINECold calling can be effective. Nobody can truly deny that but there are different phases and stages of business. Not every process, system or marketing technique is going to be the ideal choice for every stage you enter.There are many situations where cold calling is an ideal choice to grow something from nothing but if you continue only using that stream of lead generation all by yourself you’re bound to be stuck on a plateau and you’re also exposing yourself to a lot of unneeded risk.</h1><p>Cold calling and telemarketing are topics that seem to be an evergreen issue among marketers and many business owners. There’s never any closure on this issue for many though and hopefully this blog post settles some of the issues!</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/74089bf539736b7c2a3ed5218fb160894283619b.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/cold-calling-and-telemarketing-are-topics-that-seem-to-be-an/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3ab9a58b-f675-49a4-9454-1ba8a908b2cc</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:28:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[10 ROOKIE MISTAKES I MADE WHEN STARTING OUT IN BUSINESS]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>10 ROOKIE MISTAKES I MADE WHEN STARTING OUT IN BUSINESS</h1><p>In this post you’re going to learn:</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/10-rookie-mistakes-i-made-when-starting-out-in-business/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8eb4aba0-f227-44db-af62-308d4ff718ff</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:28:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LOCAL SEO RANKING FACTORS – LET’S SHED SOME NEW LIGHT]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>LOCAL SEO RANKING FACTORS – LET’S SHED SOME NEW LIGHT</h1><p>Every year the power house in the industry releases a survey of “professionals” in the local SEO arena. I’m sure most of you have heard of Moz.com and their Local SEO Ranking Factors survey that happen on a yearly basis. They take a handful of alleged experts and ask their opinions on certain things.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/local-seo-ranking-factors-lets-shed-some-new-light/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d37190ac-41cc-48a5-a893-93d5db0c1138</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:28:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HOW A VAPE STORE DOUBLED THEIR SALES WITH THESE 3 SIMPLE THINGS]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>HOW A VAPE STORE DOUBLED THEIR SALES WITH THESE 3 SIMPLE THINGS</h1><p>So I used to be a pretty heavy smoker, stress does that to you but I also enjoyed it. I quit a few different times and always went back to smoking until I started vaping. If you’re someone that has switched to vaping, you probably spend a little bit of time at your local vape shop, checking out new equipment, trying different juice flavors, and just hanging out.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/how-a-vape-store-doubled-their-sales-with-these-3-simple-thi/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2b431e7a-c13d-4a12-b5c8-121db20f989b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:28:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW TO GET STARTED]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW TO GET STARTED</h1><p>It IS fun, for the most part and there are few things better in life than being your own boss.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/3-things-to-understand-before-you-launch-a-web-design-or-seo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c56d4032-d5f5-4492-a765-3133fede7819</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:13:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Many of you know that I’m not a fan of gurus or even the people that have come highly regarded in the industry of marketing, SEO, sales, etc. I’m just not a believer in a lot of them.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/partytentclub/many-of-you-know-that-im-not-a-fan-of-gurus-or-even-the-peo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a44f1201-d2cb-4b9d-876c-0e1d5f061185</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:07:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>